Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Dewey Daane Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0098
198.75 linear_feet
- Executive Leadership Seminar on The State of the U.S. Economy: Choices for the Future, Brookings, 6/16-18/87 (Box 1)
- Graduate Program in Economic Development Conference, 10/17-19/86 (Box 1)
- DRI U.S. Economic Outlook Conf. Chicago, 12/10/87 (Box 1)
- DRI U.S. Economic Outlook Conf. NYC, 10/6/87 (Box 1)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta- Prof. Dornbusch, 9/25/87 (Box 1)
- Luncheon with Kazimir Aivko Pregl, 9/14/87 (Box 1)
- Volcker Dinner D.C., 9/3/87 (Box 1)
- Esther Seeman Director, Japan Center of Tennessee, 3/30/88 (Box 1)
- Impact Symposium, 1988 (Box 1)
- Symposium with Japanese visitors 2/2/88 “Japanese direct investments in the U.S.” “The World Currency situation” (Box 1)
- Loose Materials- World Currency (Box 1)
- Talk, 1/14/88/ (Box 1)
- Harvard Univ.4/25-26/88 Hanson-Williams Seminar (Box 1)
- Monetary Aggregates and Financial Sector Behavior in Interdependent Economies Federal Reserve Board Conf. D. C., 5/26-27/88 (Box 1)
- Loose Materials- Related to Federal Reserve Board Conf. May, 1988 (Box 1)
- Vanderbilt Intl. Week Panel Discussion and Forum 4/6/89 Speaker Frederick Summers (Box 1)
- Fed’s 75th Anniversary Dinner, 4/13/89 (Box 1)
- DEPO MA Lect. OwIBA, 3/23/89 (Box 1)
- Atlanta Federal Reserve Bank- Dr. Alan S. Greenspan Chmn Bd of Gov., 1/12/89 (Box 1)
- Frank Morris Retirement Dinner, 10/12/88 (Box 1)
- DRI U.S. Economic Outlook Conf. D.C., 6/16/88 (Box 1)
- Brookings Exec. Leadership Seminar “Choices for the Future” D.C., 6/14-16/88 (Box 1)
- Brookings Inst. Conf. D.C., 6/13-15/89 (Box 1)
- “Banking and Payment Services” 6/7-9/89 Federal Reserve Bd Sponsors Intl Symposium (Box 1)
- Vanderbilt – Current (Box 1)
- Correspondence with the Chancellor (Box 1)
- University Research Council (Box 1)
- University Club Bylaws (Box 1)
- IAP- Integrative Applied Projects (Box 1)
- Advantage Magazine Series (Box 1)
- Nashville Banner- Bd of Contributors (Box 1)
- National Futures Association (Box 1)
- High Level Economic Conf. Wiggington Secession (Box 1)
- VIPPS U.S.- Japan Roundtable (Box 1)
- VIPPS Discussion group on History and Politics (Box 1)
- VIPPS- Inst. For Public Policy Studies (Box 1)
- Beta Gamma Sigma (Box 1)
- Vanderbilt Journal of Transnational Law- Consultant and Advisor (Box 1)
- Ewing Shahan (Box 1)
- William B. Dale “The IMF and the World Economy” OLS, 1/19/87 (Box 2)
- Southeast U.S./ Japan Association 11th Annual Meeting 10/12-14/86 Hot Springs, VA (Box 2)
- Debt Busters, 9/10/86 (Box 2)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta Reception for Manuel Johnson, 6/12/86 (Box 2)
- National Issues Forum Economic Choices 1987 Brookings Inst., 5/28/86 (Box 2)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta 11/14-15/85 “The Southeast in a Dynamic Global Economy…” J.D.D. (Box 2)
- Industrial Bd Conf. NY 9/20/84 Waldolf Hotel (Box 2)
- Impact Symposium 2/12-13/82 “Conservatism” A Mandate from the People?” (Box 2)
- Belmont College Long Range Planning Meeting, 3/26/81 (Box 2)
- Inflation Task Force Panel Meeting, 11/9/80 (Box 2)
- Inflation Policy Task Force Nov, 1980 (Box 2)
- Vanderbilt Impact Symposium “the Election”, 3/15/80 (Box 2)
- Discussion with Treasury and Federal Reserve Officials (including Volcker), 9/7/79 (Box 2)
- American Economic Association Meetings NY Dec, 1977 (Box 2)
- Visit with the President, 1/25/75 (Box 2)
- Wallenburg Bankers Forum, 9/28/87 Georgetown (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 28th Annual Bankers Forum, 9/28/81 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 32nd Annual Bankers Forum, 11/1/85 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 31st Annual Bankers Forum, 9/22/84 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 30th Annual Bankers Forum, 9/26/83 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 28th Annual Bankers Forum, 9/28/81 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University Bankers Forum, 9/29/80 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 24th Annual Bankers Forum, 9/30/77 (Box 2)
- Georgetown University 21st Annual Bankers Forum, 10/4-5/74 (Box 2)
- Clippings- July, 1990 (Box 2)
- Personal Notes (Box 2)
- Proposed Financial Institutions Act of 1976- Letter to Clifford Allen, 2/76 (Box 2)
- Letter to Clifford Allen (Box 2)
- Faculty Research Committee (Box 3)
- New Management Library (Box 3)
- OGSM Computer Resources (Box 3)
- Proposals re Management School (Box 3)
- Library Meeting, 5/5/83 (Box 3)
- OGSM Asso. Program (Box 3)
- Faculty Candidates (Box 3)
- Potter Chair Search (Box 3)
- Dean Search (Box 3)
- Inauguration Advisory Committee (Box 3)
- Coles Memorial (Box 3)
- Flournoy A. Coles, Jr. (Box 3)
- OGSM Budgets (Box 3)
- Faculty Meetings (Box 3)
- Placement (Box 3)
- OGSM- General (Box 3)
- Tenured Faculty Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
- Tenured Faculty Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
- Tenured Faculty Meetings, 9/12/85 and 4/24/86 (Box 3)
- Meetings of Full Professors- Prof. Rados’ Home, 9/12/84, 10/3/84, and 10/15/84 (Box 3)
- Faculty Meeting Standards of Performance, 1/12/84 (Box 3)
- Discussion in Dean’s Conf. Rm., 11/10/83 (Box 3)
- Faculty Research Seminars, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
- Owen Lecture Series (Box 3)
- Potter Lecture Series (Box 3)
- Robert Z. Aliber “Financial Innovation, 4/14/87 (Box 3)
- ITT Key Issues Lecture Series, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
- Caperton Memorial Lectureship (Box 3)
- OSSA Speakers (Box 3)
- OwIBA, 1990 (Box 3)
- OwIBA (Box 3)
- Financial Workshop (Box 3)
- Financial Markets Research Center Spring Meeting, 4/7-8/88 (Box 3)
- Financial Markets Research Center (Box 3)
- Doctoral Program (Box 3)
- Folder- BOA Meeting, Apr 4-6, 1991 (Box 4)
- BOA Meeting - Reference Materials (Box 4)
- BOA Meeting - Apr 4-6 Lexington, KY (Box 4)
- Craig Bruns Dissertation, 1991 (Box 4)
- Career Day-, Oct 18, 1991 (Box 4)
- Diesel Sales and Service Board Meeting, 1/17/92 (Box 4)
- Diesel Sales and Service/ Victoria Jackson (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1991 (Box 4)
- Correspondence, 1990 (Box 4)
- Joe Cowell- Parthenon Futures (Box 4)
- Catherine C. Earthman (Box 4)
- EMBA, 1991-92 (Box 4)
- EMBA, 1990-91 (Box 4)
- Expenses, 1991 (Box 4)
- Expenses, 1990 (Box 4)
- Annual Report of Faculty Activities, 1989 (Box 4)
- Budget/ Charges, 1989/1990 (Box 4)
- Edwards Case (Box 4)
- Conf. on Financial Markets Transaction Costs, 4/11/91 (Box 4)
- IMF (Expenses) (Box 4)
- FRB of Boston Conf. 6/16-18/91 “The Fin. Condition and Regulation of Ins. Companies” (Box 4)
- IBAA Bank Investments May 10-15, 1992 (Box 4)
- “Policy Implications of the Trade and Currency Zones” Symposium Aug 22-23, 1991 (Box 4)
- USA Today –Apr, 1992 (Box 4)
- Faculty Meeting, 9/16/94 (Box 4)
- MSG- Fill (Box 4)
- Bios- Feb, 1993 (Box 4)
- Spring, 1993 (Box 4)
- Luncheon List (Box 4)
- Monetary and Fiscal Policy(Judy Stephens) (Box 4)
- - Luncheon, Jan 1993 (Box 4)
- - Luncheon, Feb 1993 (Box 4)
- - Lunch Letters, Apr 1993 (Box 4)
- - Seminar Letters- Luncheon, Mar 1993 (Box 4)
- Luncheon Expenses for Spring Seminars, 1993 (Box 4)
- Spring 1993- Reserve Materials (Box 4)
- Jackson Hole Trip (Box 4)
- FRB of Kansas City Symposium- Jackson Hole, WY, Aug 23-25, 1990 (Box 4)
- Peter Juhos (Box 4)
- V.S. Johnson Articles (Box 4)
- Medical, 1990 (Box 4)
- National Association of Bank Directors (Box 4)
- OwIBA, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
- NFA Meeting Chicago, Jan 8, 1992 (Box 4)
- NFA Meeting Chicago, Jan 8, 1992 (Box 4)
- Loose- NFA Materials (Box 4)
- Luncheons for Seminar- Spring, 1991 (Box 5)
- Max Adler (Box 5)
- Conf. On Bank Structure and Competition FRB of Chicago, 5/11-12/88 (Box 5)
- Weaver C. Barksdale (Box 5)
- Seminar Dinner Expenses, 1986 (Box 5)
- Seminar Speakers (Box 5)
- [Computer Printouts of Business Movement of Select Companies] (Box 5)
- Loose- Materials on Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy, 1976-1980 (Box 5)
- [15 Hanging file folders with Wall Street Journal Index from 1970 with highlighting] (Box 5)
- Guest Speakers Spring, 1993 (Box 6)
- DSS- 1993 Audit Report (Box 6)
- Funston Application (Box 6)
- Vanderbilt Applicants (Box 6)
- FOMP REF, 94 (Box 6)
- Macroeconomics EMGT 721 Spring, 1993 (Box 6)
- MGT Seminar, 93-94 (Box 6)
- Matt Wigginton High Level Economic Conf., Apr 22, 1993 (Box 6)
- MGT 524, Spr 1993 (Box 6)
- Manager Info, 1993 (Box 6)
- Appointments/Meetings attended by Prof. Daane (Box 6)
- Luncheon Expenses for Spring Seminars, 1992 (Box 6)
- Spring Break trip/ Eastern Europe, 1992 (Box 6)
- Fax from Wall Street Journal (Box 6)
- Weekly Calendar, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
- Back-up File (Box 6)
- Purchase Orders, 1992 (Box 6)
- Sample Letters for Seminar Speakers (Box 6)
- -Seminar Outline Speakers, 1991 (Box 6)
- Fax Copies (Box 6)
- Chronological File (Outgoing) (Box 6)
- Correspondence (Incoming) (Box 6)
- FRB of Chicago The Changing Financial Structure and Its Implication- VU, Mar 30, 1994 (Box 6)
- Outgoing-, 1994 (Box 6)
- General, 1994 (Box 6)
- Incoming, 1994 (Box 6)
- Fax, 1994 (Box 6)
- Special Topics (Box 6)
- Monetary and Fiscal Policy- Spring 94- Syllabus and Reading List (Box 6)
- NAEFA Session-, Jan 6-8, 1995 (Box 6)
- NFA- NYC, Nov 17, 1994 (Box 6)
- 30th Annual Conf. On Bank Structure May 11-13, 1994- Chicago (Box 6)
- British American Business Association of Tennessee (Box 6)
- Monthly Calendar, 1993-1994 (Box 6)
- Exhibits- Meeting of the Subcommittee for the Review of Non-Performance related Disclosure Issues, Nov 16, 1994 NY (Box 6)
- Disclosure Committee Meeting NFA (Box 6)
- NFA-, Feb 8, 1994 (Box 6)
- NFA- May 19, 1994 Board of Directors Meeting NY (Box 6)
- NFA, May 18-19, 1994 NY (Box 6)
- NFA-, Jan 1994 (Box 6)
- Board of Directors Meeting - NFA, May 19, 1994 NY (Box 6)
- [Recruiting Info] (Box 7)
- [Applicants for Owen position- rejection letters] (Box 7)
- FRB of Kansas City Symposium 8/22-25/91 Jackson Hole, Wy (Box 7)
  - FRB of Boston Conf-, Jun 1991 (Box 7)
  - EMBA, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Brian Coyne (Box 7)
- NFA- Board of Directors, Aug 15, 1991 NY (Box 7)
- Special Committee- NFA (Box 7)
- NFA- Board of Directors Nov 21, 1991 Chicago (Box 7)
- NFA Meeting, (3/26/91) (Box 7)
- New York, 11/16/90 (Box 7)
- David Parsley (Box 7)
- Prime Times- Dr. Everette James, 9/18/90 (Box 7)
- Ken Roberts (Box 7)
- NFA (Box 7)
- NFA- Proposed Budget for Fiscal, 1992 (Box 7)
- International Finance and Financial Policy- Conf. Honoring JDD on his retirement for Vanderbilt University, Apr. 13-14, 1989 (Box 7)
- Responses (Box 7)
- International Finance and Financial Policy- Conf. Honoring JDD on his retirement for Vanderbilt University, Apr. 13-14, 1989 (Box 7)
- International Finance and Financial Policy- Conf. Honoring JDD on his retirement for Vanderbilt University, Apr. 13-14, 1989 (Box 7)
- International Finance and Financial Policy- Conf. Honoring JDD on his retirement for Vanderbilt University, Apr. 13-14, 1989 (Box 7)
- International Finance and Financial Policy- Conf. Honoring JDD on his retirement for Vanderbilt University, Apr. 13-14, 1989 (Box 7)
- Spring Conf. (Box 7)
- St. L Crisis (Box 7)
- Advisory Board of Southwest LBO Fund, 4/22/91 (Box 7)
- St. George’s Episcopal Church (Box 7)
- St. George’s Vestry Meeting, 12/16/91 (Box 7)
- St. George’s Retreat 2/8-10/91 Monteagle (Box 7)
- Swan Ball Award, 1991 Swan Ball Award, 1990 (Box 7)
- Faculty Expense Allowance, 1991 (Box 7)
- JDD 1991 V-net telephone Billing (Box 7)
- Interoffice (VU) Memos, 1991 (Box 7)
- Wall Street Journal Forecast, 1/1/91 (Box 7)
- Wash/NY Trips (Box 7)
- USA Today Survey (Box 7)
- Visiting Foreign Correspondents 2/20/92 OGSM (Box 7)
- High Level Economic Conf., 10/27/94 (Box 8)
- Travel, 1993 (Box 8)
- Spring 93- Seminar Billing (Box 8)
- Special Committee- NFA (Box 8)
- The Alfalfa Club-, 1/28/94 D.C. (Box 8)
- Federal Reserve, 3/11/94 (Box 8)
- Eastern Economic Association Boston, 3/18/94 (Box 8)
- [Ballots] (Box 8)
- Regular Annual Meeting of the Board of Directors- NFA, 2/24/94 NY (Box 8)
- NFA- Board of Directors Meeting, 2/24/94 NY (Box 8)
- NFA Proposed Budget for Fiscal Year, 1995 (Box 8)
- Finance Committee Meeting 4/5/94 NFA (Box 8)
- Special Committee for the Review of CPO/CTA Disclosure Issues 5/18/94 NFA (Box 8)
- Subcommittee for the Review of Non-Performance Disclosure Issues 5/18/94 NFA (Box 8)
- NFA Meeting Chicago, Apr 5, 1994 (Box 8)
- NFA Proposed Budget for Fiscal, 1995 (Box 8)
- FRB of Kansas City Symposium- Jackson Hole, Wy, 8/25-27/94 (Box 8)
- Board of Directors Meeting NFA, 11/17/94 NY (Box 8)
- Towards a paperless registration process NFA, 11/17/94 (Box 8)
- NFA- Financial statements (Box 8)
- NFA Board Meeting, 11/17/94 NY (Box 8)
- Subcommittee for the Review of the Non-performance related disclosure issues 12/16/94 NFA NY (Box 8)
- Bretton Woods Commission Meeting, 7/20-22/94 DC (Box 8)
- NFA- Chicago, 9/15/94 (Box 8)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Kansas City- Jackson Hole, Wy, 8/25-27/94 (Box 8)
- DSS/Prodiesel Meeting, 4/17/94 (Box 8)
- [13 Copies- The Federal Reserve System- Purposes and Functions] (Box 8)
- CBO Study- Feb 1993 Displaced Workers (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Apr 1993 Resolving the Thrift Crisis (Box 9)
- CBO Study- May 1993 Managed Competition and its potential to reduce health spending (Box 9)
- CBO Study- May 1992 Paying for Highways, Airways and Waterways (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jan 1992 The Economic Effects of the Saving and Loan Crisis (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jul 1993 A Budgetary and Economic Analysis of NAFTA (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jan 1993 Controlling Losses of the Pension Benefit Guaranty System (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jul 1993 The Federal Home Loan Banks in the Housing Finance System (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jul 1993 Using Performance Measures in the Federal Budget Process (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jun 1993 Trends in Health Spending: An Update (Box 9)
- CBO Study-Sep 1993 Baby Boomers in Retirement: An Early Perspective (Box 9)
- CBO Study-May 1993 The Fed. Role in Improving Elementary and Secondary Education (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Jun 1992 The Outlook for Farm Commodity Program Spending Fiscal Years, 1992-1997 (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 4/29/92 James L. Blum (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 4/7/92 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 6/10/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 5/4/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 4/20/93 Ralph E. Smith (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 1/27/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 1/26/93 Nancy M. Gordon (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 3/10/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 3/10/93 James L. Blum (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 3/4/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 2/24/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 2/17/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 2/10/93 Paul Cullinan (Box 9)
- CBO Testimony- 2/3/93 Robert D. Reischauer (Box 9)
- CBO Study- Apr 1993 Assessing the Decline in the National Savings Rate (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Feb 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, May 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Jun 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Jul 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Aug 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Sep 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Oct 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Nov 1993 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin- Dec 1993 [2 Copies] (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Nov 1992 (Box 9)
- Federal Reserve Bulletin-, Dec 1992 (Box 9)
- 2 Folders- The Japan Center of Tennessee (Box 9)
- Monetary Policy Objectives- Midyear review of the FRB, 1994; 7/20/94 (Box 9)
- The Manager, Vol. 15 No 2 Spring 1994- OGSM (Box 9)
- Joint Report on the Government Securities Market, Jun 1992 (Box 9)
- Economic Review Sep/Oct 1993 Vol. 78 No 5 FRB of Atlanta (Box 9)
- Privatization in Eastern and Central Europe- Group of 30 Occasional Paper 34 (Box 9)
- The American Enterprise, May/June 1993 (Box 9)
- Bank Director Vol. 3 No 2 2nd Quarter, 1993 (Box 9)
- Occasional Papers IMF Feb 1994 “The Russian Federation in Transition External Developments (Box 9)
- International Banking and Financial Market Developments-, May 1994 (Box 9)
- Seminar: International Management Issues- Czechoslovakia and Hungary (Box 9)
- Owen- Conf. On World trading Markets, 4/9-10/92 (Box 9)
- Seminar Papers (Box 9)
  - Learning from the Pioneers: A Case Study of Western Direct Investment in Czechoslovakia and Hungary, 4/30/92 (Box 9)
  - The Development of a Financial System: A Case Study of Hungary and Czechoslovakia, 4/30/92 (Box 9)
- Seminar: International Management Issues Mgt 555 (Box 9)
- International Finance and Economics- Reference Materials Fall, 1988 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Course #424 Fall, 1988 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture #1 (Mork and Daane), 8/31/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Course #424 (Mork’s Materials), 9/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Mid Term Exam, 10/12/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 2, 10/19/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 3, 10/26/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 4, 11/2/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 5, 11/9/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Pre Exam Meeting with Class, 12/2/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Final Exam, 12/14/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 6, 11/16/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 7, 11/30/88 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Reference Materials Fall, 1987 (Box 10)
- International (Box 10)
- Mexico (Box 10)
- Envelope—Bisingnano Research (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Course #424 Fall, 1987 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 1 (Mork and Daane), 9/2/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 2 and #3 (Mork), 9/9/87 and 9/16/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 4 (Mork) 9/23/87“Balance of Payments” (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 5 (Mork) 9/30/87 #6, 10/7/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 7, 10/21/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 8, 10/28/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 9, 11/4/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 10, 11/11/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 11, 11/18/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Lecture # 12, 12/2/87 (Box 10)
- International Finance and Economics- Mid term exam 10/14/87 Final Exam, 12/11/87 (Box 10)
- Study of U.S. Business in Japan Original Folder (OwIBA) –MGT 559 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance- Class #1, 9/22/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance- Class #2, 10/5/88 (Box 10)
- Mgt 559- Special Topics: International Management (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class #3, 10/31/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class #4, 11/2/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class #5, 11/4/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class # 6, 11/16/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class #7, 11/30/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance Class #8, 12/14/88 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance, 2/22/89 (Box 10)
- 559- Special Topics: International Finance, 4/20/89 (Box 10)
- Envelope- [ 7 papers on Strong Dollar] (Box 11)
- Mexico (Box 11)
- G-5 Intervention (Box 11)
- Draft- Highlights in the Evolution of the Intl. Monetary System Since Bretton Woods (Box 11)
- Statement by Paul Volcker to Committee on Foreign Affairs- House of Rep. (Box 11)
- Hearing on Conduct of Monetary Policy 7/25/84 Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Policy (Box 11)
- IMF/ World Bank- News Clips, 1984 (Box 11)
- IMF Quota Increase Mid Year, 1983 (Box 11)
- IMF Speeches and Clippings, 10/83 (Box 11)
- Issues for Annual IMF Meetings (IMF), 9/27/83 (Box 11)
- European Monetary System (Box 11)
- WLAC International Economy, 8/23/93 (Box 11)
- WLAC Williamsburg Summit, 8/23/83 (Box 11)
- Talk to Stan Black’s Class and John Vahally’s Class, 12/10/74 (Box 11)
- Remarks to Prof. Fels’ Class, 10/14/75 (Box 11)
- Gold Commission (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1988 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1987 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1986 (Box 11)
- 436 International Finance and Economics Lecture #8b- Regulation of Foreign Banking, 11/26/80 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1985 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1984 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1983 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1982 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1981 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #424 Fall, 1980 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #532 Fall, 1979 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Class Fall, 1978 (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course #532 Fall, 1977 (Box 11)
- International Finance, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
- Exams (Box 11)
- Loose- 2 Pieces on Euro Currency (Box 11)
- Lecture #8 12/4/85 Reference Materials (Box 11)
- International Finance and Economics Course # 532 Lecture #11, 11/28/77 (Box 11)
- Conf. On Foreign Banking Regulation Jun 18, 1974 Sponsored by Salomon Brothers (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking- CIEP (Box 12)
- Foreign Lending Facilities (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking Regulations Draft Bill (Box 12)
- Statistics on Bank Operations in Recent Crisis, 4/73 (Box 12)
- - Steering Committee on Intl Banking Regulations (W/ BAFT), Feb 19, 1974 (Box 12)
- System Steering Committee in Intl Banking Regulations-, 1974 (Box 12)
- - Breakfast Meeting with Conf. Of State Bank Supervisors, Sep 14, 1973 (Box 12)
- U.S. Views on Major Issues of Monetary Reform, August 27, 1973 (Box 12)
- - Meeting of System Steering Committee on Intl Banking Regulation, Aug 8, 1973 (Box 12)
- System Steering Committee on Intl Banking Regulation, 1973 (Box 12)
- London/Paris May 25- Jun 1, 1974 Foreign Banking (Box 12)
- Oct 18-19, 1973- Tokyo Meetings with Bank of Japan and Commercial Bankers (Box 12)
- Briefing Book- Governors Mitchell and Daane trip to Japan Oct, 1973 (Box 12)
- - Ottawa Meeting at Bank of Canada, Mar 4-5, 1973 (Box 12)
- - New York Meetings on Foreign Banking, Feb 14, 1973 (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking in U.S. –Denmark/Italy/France/Switzerland/England Meetings, 11/1-16/72 (Box 12)
- Visits of Messrs Meyjes and Muller (Netherlands), 10/5/72 (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking in U.S. – England/ Germany/ Netherlands Meetings, 5/23-28/72 (Box 12)
- Banco Di Roma (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking in U.S. Master Folder, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
- Part I Summary Report and Issues Papers- Report of Task Force on Foreign Operations of U.S. Banks, Aug 1972 (Box 12)
- Part II Study Papers- Report of Task Force on Foreign Operations of U.S. Banks, Aug 1972 (Box 12)
- Foreign Banking (Box 12)
- Regulation K: Foreign Banking (Box 12)
- Regulation M: Foreign Activities, National Banks (Box 12)
- Regulations M and D: Foreign Activities(M) Reserve Requirements (D) (Box 12)
- Branches- “Shell” Foreign (Box 12)
- Foreign Bank Holding Co Applications (Box 12)
- Foreign Bank Holding Co General (Box 12)
- Binder- [ Contingency Planning- Assessment of the Need of Sterling Devaluation] (Box 12)
- Paul Volcker (Box 13)
- New York Times Magazine Article on Paul Volcker (Box 13)
- Prof. David Wightman, Univ. of Birmingham (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- EMB (Ltd.)- Edward M. Bernstein Research Reports (Box 13)
- Future Structure of Finance System (Box 13)